Contact

Cantt, lahore. Pakistan +923244562432 (Home) inamullahkhan1032@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/inam-ullah-khan-242374118 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
HTML
Visual Studio
C++

Inam Ullah Khan

SSE (.Net Core | React JS | TDD | Azure| Al Enthusiast | Python | Machine Learning)

Pakistan

Summary

I'm a software solution provider having 4 years of experience through a time commitment, contributing to the company's growth and in turn ensuring personal growth within the organization. I believe that my technical, functional and communication skills will enable me in facing the challenging career ahead. A challenging position is a software development and possibility of career growth. I'm a disciplined, enthusiastic and hard working person. I have a flexible attitude, and have always displayed a desire to excel in all that I do. I possess good leadership, communication and organizational skills and my attitude to work and study has always been of a flexible and versatile nature. I feel this approach enables me to improve my own learning and performance, meeting the performance expectations and contributing to the overall success of everything. My aim is to gain employment, with a company who recognizes commitment, determination and above all, innovation amongst its employees, in order to meet objectives.

Experience

TkXel

2 years 9 months

Senior Software Engineer
June 2019 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Lahore, Pakistan

Software Engineer

January 2019 - June 2019 (6 months)

Lahore, Pakistan

C# | ASP.NET Core | ASP.NET MVC | React | JavaScript | Web Services | Web APIs | WCF

Intagleo Systems Software Engineer November 2016 - December 2018 (2 years 2 months)

Lahore, pakistan

Brisk Solution pvt ltd software Engineer January 2016 - November 2016 (11 months) Lahore,Pakistan

Microsoft innovation center lahore ASP.NET as well as UWP development May 2016 - October 2016 (6 months) Lahore.Pakistan

ASP.NET as well as UWP development as internee at Microsoft innovation center lahore

EVS Professional Training Institute Inernee January 2016 - July 2016 (7 months)

Microsoft internee 2016 - 2016 (less than a year)

Education

LAHORE GARRISION UNIVERSITY BSCS · (2012 - 2016)